For your final coding exercise, we're going to take, we're going to do a week
story with Pena. I recommend doing it doing the setup way just because just to get
more opportunities to practice that. And then kind of see how it feels. And then if you
can, see if you can get it to show up inside of your dev tools and then play around with
like, and again, you can even just stub out the data. You don't have to worry too much about
like, whether it works with the entire app or not, the idea here is to get you getting
some time with Pena and set of sort. Okay, so we have the use week composed of what that we
created together. And so you can see here, it's funny when you're looking at these side
by sides. Let me open up the use tasks or task store. So what it is. If you look at them, they're actually
not so different. It's kind of interesting. And so the main thing being that, you know, by opting
into this defined store helper, there's a bunch of stuff that Pena will do for you, but from
like a structure perspective, we're actually fairly fairly close there. So basically what I would
do here is we would say, all right, so X-Ball export, cons, use week store, right, and we'll define
the store. And I usually basically just call the key whatever the store name is, just to be consistent.
And then we open it up with set function. So I'm just going to go ahead and do it like that,
and then I'll close this now, just to give us our space back. And then let's just make sure we go
it back down here, to make sure we get it right, although something looks funny, bump bump bump.
That's good, that const async. Okay, that's good. Because of the return. Oh, this is all the way up here.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, okay. Got it. So let's just, let me permanently comment this out so that
this is not confusing, but you also have it, too.
Okay, now this part is good, this part is not.
Yes, good, and then, okay, we need to import the fine store
from pinnea, which is great, there we have it.
And then, as you can see, we already have our actions in our getter,
so really what we need is just the state.
And the state is all of the things we see here,
so we can just grab this, I mean,
it's gonna break a ton of things,
because we know what happened last time I did this.
But, this is the start.
So here's our weeks, da, da, da, exposed,
and then everything else here.
And so this is where, at this point,
I'm just not gonna bother with the read-only pattern,
because we are in a store now,
and I personally and not so convince that we need that.
So there we go, Shred, state, this is it.
And then, yep, that's the store.
And then, actually, I think,
we actually don't even need this anymore, right?
Yeah, we don't.
Yep.
So then, this here then gets moved all the way down
into stores, okay, and then we call it week store, okay.
Okay, and now, I think there's gonna be a bunch of stuff
that's gonna ultimately end up breaking,
because this does not work the way we want it to,
but we're gonna not gonna worry about that,
just for the moment, we're just gonna ask any questions
about sort of that convergence.
Does anyone have any issues with that migration path?
Thought overall familiar, given what we've been doing?
Good, that's a good sign for me,
because we felt different than, yeah, I mean,
that I think when Eduardo was doing the design spec
for PENIA or essentially what is UX5,
it was this idea that, like, composition already API already,
just has that light flexibility that clearly
a lot of people have gravitated towards,
and we really didn't want to step that far away from it.
There was no point designing a whole new API
just to, like, just because of the state management library.
And so, yeah, so with that, that is your use week store.
And let's see, is there anything else I had us do?
Nope, composing stores, PENIA DevTools.
I think that's mostly that.
As the final result, there will be a branch,
that's called like solution,
and I'll basically make sure everything
is at least talking to each other correctly,
and that way, like, we can see how it all works together
in the end.
But again, I wanted to kind of create a really a playground
for you all, whereas, like, I mean,
this is what it's like working in some,
honestly, some co-bases, right?
Stuff's broken, stuff's weirdly dependent,
there's some weird things are written in some funny ways.
It's a how we make sense of that over time,
and organize that, you know, make K,
sorry, make order out of chaos,
stuff the other way around.
Yeah, I mean, that's really what we're trying to do as developers.
So, yeah, there'll be some,
and I'll make sure it's indicated on the repo,
like, whatever, I probably would just call it solution.
All right.